RALPH MATTHEW D. PUNZALAN

ralphmatthewpunzalan23@gmail.com | 0945-338-6067 | Centro, Santo Tomas Isabela

SUMMARY

I am Ralph Matthew Delarosa Punzalan, a BSIT student skilled in graphic design, React.js development, and UI/UX design. I enjoy creating user-friendly websites and appealing designs. I aim to use my skills to build great projects that improve the user experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

React JS Developer (Part Time)

Aug 2024 - Oct 2024

- E-commerce App Development (Capstone Project): Developed the front end of a
 mobile e-commerce app for a client. Implemented product listings, shopping cart,
 payment options (COD, GCash), and order tracking and focused on building a
 professional and user-friendly interface using React Native and Expo Router,
 ensuring smooth navigation and responsive layouts on mobile devices.
- Quiz Whirl App: Built the front end of an interactive quiz app with multiple question types and score tracking. I designed a responsive and engaging user interface using React Native, ensuring smooth performance across various mobile devices.

Graphic Designer (Part Time at Upwork)

Jan 2024 - Feb 2024

- Completed projects such as Logo Designer
- Completed final touches for projects before deadline.
- · Completed projects such as Poster.
- Designed creative digital displays used in online advertising for local businesses.

Employee as GIP (LGU STO TOMAS)

June 2024 - Nov 2024

- Edited banners for LGU (Local Government Unit) and designed a book cover.
- Edited publication materials (pubmats) and newspapers.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology University of Saint Louis Tuguegarao Tuguegarao City, Cagayan 2020 - 2024

CERTIFICATES

- Computer System Servicing NC II 2023
- Certificate of Appreciation Philippine Society of Information Technology Educators (PSITE), 4th ICITE 2023
- Gawad San Luis for Excellence in Innovation, Creativity, and Agility- University of Saint Louis, 2024

KEY SKILLS

- UI/UX Designer (Mobile and Web)
- · React JS Developer

- Graphic Designer
- Technical Support (Computer Hardware)

PROJECTS

LaborLinkz: Building Community Through Freelancing Platform

 Developed a mobile platform connecting blue-collar workers with local job opportunities, enhancing employment accessibility and supporting local economies.